export const data = [
    {
        Question: 'What is Redux?',
        Option1: 'Redux is Data Type',
        Option2: 'Redux is a Part of HTML',
        Option3: 'Redux is State Management System',
        Option4: 'Redux is State',
        correctAnswer: 'Option3'
    },
    {
        Question: 'What is the core principle of Redux?',
        Option1: 'No State Management',
        Option2: 'Component-Based State',
        Option3: 'Multiple States',
        Option4: 'Single Source of Truth',
        correctAnswer: 'Option4'
    },
    {
        Question: 'What is an Action in Redux?',
        Option1: 'A type of middleware',
        Option2: 'An object describing what happened',
        Option3: 'A method to update state',
        Option4: 'A reducer function',
        correctAnswer: 'Option2'
    },
    {
        Question: 'What is a Reducer in Redux?',
        Option1: 'A function to handle state changes based on actions',
        Option2: 'A way to create store',
        Option3: 'A part of React component',
        Option4: 'A method to dispatch actions',
        correctAnswer: 'Option1'
    },
    {
        Question: 'What is the purpose of the Redux store?',
        Option1: 'Holds the application state',
        Option2: 'Handles middleware',
        Option3: 'Defines the reducers',
        Option4: 'Renders the UI',
        correctAnswer: 'Option1'
    },
    {
        Question: 'What is the role of middleware in Redux?',
        Option1: 'Creates the store',
        Option2: 'Defines actions',
        Option3: 'Updates the state directly',
        Option4: 'Handles asynchronous actions',
        correctAnswer: 'Option4'
    },
    {
        Question: 'Which library is often used with Redux for asynchronous operations?',
        Option1: 'React-Context',
        Option2: 'React-Router',
        Option3: 'Redux-Thunk',
        Option4: 'Redux-Store',
        correctAnswer: 'Option3'
    },
    {
        Question: 'What is the syntax to create a Redux store?',
        Option1: 'storeRedux()',
        Option2: 'generateStore()',
        Option3: 'createStore(reducer)',
        Option4: 'useStore(reducer)',
        correctAnswer: 'Option3'
    },
    {
        Question: 'What does the `dispatch` method do in Redux?',
        Option1: 'Defines a reducer',
        Option2: 'Creates an action',
        Option3: 'Updates the state directly',
        Option4: 'Sends an action to the store',
        correctAnswer: 'Option4'
    },
    {
        Question: 'What is the purpose of `combineReducers` in Redux?',
        Option1: 'Dispatches actions',
        Option2: 'Combines multiple reducers into one',
        Option3: 'Creates the Redux store',
        Option4: 'Splits state into components',
        correctAnswer: 'Option2'
    }
];
